A Guide to the Lucille P. Markey Charitable Trust records FA017
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Scholars and Visiting Fellows, 1983-1998; 1
  - Scholar Applicants, 1983-1998; 1
    - Denied Applicants, 1984-1990; B
      - Flack, John M. - Application 880115 (Reel 46, Frame 972)
      - Ross, Brian D. - Application 880116 (Reel 46, Frame 1007)
      - Trimmer, James S. - Application 880117 (Reel 46, Frame 1043)
      - Pendergast, Ann Marie - Application 880118 (Reel 46, Frame 1076)
      - Mannon, Peter J. - Application 880119 (Reel 46, Frame 1109)
      - McCamant-Grigsby, Susan K. - Application 880120 (Reel 46, Frame 1141)
      - Matthews, Beverley B. - Application 880121 (Reel 46, Frame 1165)
      - Hartenstein, Volker - Application 880122 (Reel 46, Frame 1192)
      - Huff, Vicki - Application 880123 (Reel 47, Frame 1)
      - Lee, Je Ho - Application 880124 (Reel 47, Frame 34)
      - Dale, William E. - Application 880125 (Reel 47, Frame 73)
      - Cone, Richard W. - Application 880126 (Reel 47, Frame 105)
      - Thomas, William J. - Application 880127 (Reel 47, Frame 134)
      - Kazlauskas, Andrius - Application 880128 (Reel 47, Frame 165)
      - Evans, Robert K. - Application 880129 (Reel 47, Frame 193)
      - Danto, Spencer I. - Application 880130 (Reel 47, Frame 234)
      - Bera, Tanmoy - Application 880131 (Reel 47, Frame 267)
      - Terada, Lance S. - Application 880132 (Reel 47, Frame 293)
      - Vivino, Frederick B. - Application 880133 (Reel 47, Frame 331)
      - Ascoli, Carl A. - Application 880134 (Reel 47, Frame 364)
      - Bedrosian, Camille L. - Application 880137 (Reel 47, Frame 393)
      - Allingham, David G. - Application 880138 (Reel 47, Frame 422)
      - Ringquist, Steven M. - Application 880139 (Reel 47, Frame 451)
      - Malinow, Roberto - Application 880141 (Reel 47, Frame 477)
      - Sachs, Alan B. - Application 880142 (Reel 47, Frame 508)
      - Sibley, Laurence D. - Application 880143 (Reel 47, Frame 539)
      - Mann, Richard S. - Application 880144 (Reel 47, Frame 575)
      - Knoper, Steven R. - Application 880145 (Reel 47, Frame 604)
      - Pagliaro, Leonard J. - Application 880146 (Reel 47, Frame 639)
      - Correa, Enrique J. - Application 890001 (Reel 47, Frame 672)
      - Houenou, Lucien J. B. - Application 890002 (Reel 47, Frame 701)
      - Cullen, Kevin J. - Application 890003 (Reel 47, Frame 734)
      - Burgess, Teresa L. - Application 890004 (Reel 47, Frame 763)
      - Barnett, Vincent A. - Application 890005 (Reel 47, Frame 796)
      - Drain, Peter - Application 890009 (Reel 47, Frame 824)
      - Garcia-Blanco, Mariano A. - Application 890010 (Reel 47, Frame 860)
      - Groisman, Eduardo A. - Application 890013 (Reel 47, Frame 892)
      - Howard, Randy L. - Application 890014 (Reel 47, Frame 927)
      - Onaivi, Emmanuel S. - Application 890015 (Reel 47, Frame 957)
      - Batzer, Mark A. - Application 890016 (Reel 47, Frame 988)
      - Vockley, Gerard - Application 890017 (Reel 47, Frame 1020)
      - Myers, Richard S. - Application 890018 (Reel 47, Frame 1056)
      - Thomas, Jennifer S. - Application 890019 (Reel 47, Frame 1084)
      - Kraegel, Susal A. - Application 890020 (Reel 47, Frame 1112)
      - Kurland, Irwin J. - Application 890021 (Reel 47, Frame 1138)
      - Hoeffler, James P. - Application 890022 (Reel 47, Frame 1169)
      - Lin, Xinli - Application 890023 (Reel 48, Frame 1)
      - Datta, Sumana - Application 890024 (Reel 48, Frame 32)
      - Aley, Stephen B. - Application 890025 (Reel 48, Frame 64)
      - Gesek, Frank A. - Application 890027 (Reel 48, Frame 100)
      - Phillips, Gregg D. - Application 890028 (Reel 48, Frame 130)
      - Scholz, Kenneth P. - Application 890029 (Reel 48, Frame 158)
      - Frankel, Wayne N. - Application 890030 (Reel 48, Frame 189)
      - Abercrombie, Elizabeth D. - Application 890031 (Reel 48, Frame 222)
      - McClain, David J. - Application 890032 (Reel 48, Frame 259)
      - McCauley, Laurie K. - Application 890033 (Reel 48, Frame 300)
      - Peng, Yan-Yi - Application 890034 (Reel 48, Frame 337)
      - Berry-Kravis, Elizabeth - Application 890035 (Reel 48, Frame 365)
      - Virgin, Herbert W., IV - Application 890036 (Reel 48, Frame 401)
      - Heckman, Charles J. - Application 890037 (Reel 48, Frame 444)
      - Ferguson, Edwin L., Jr. - Application 890038 (Reel 48, Frame 470)
      - Liang, Meina - Application 890039 (Reel 48, Frame 498)
      - Everett, Allen D. - Application 890040 (Reel 48, Frame 530)
      - Harrison, Madaline B. - Application 890041 (Reel 48, Frame 566)
      - Martin, Christopher H. - Application 890042 (Reel 48, Frame 597)
      - Lenz, H. Juergen - Application 890043 (Reel 48, Frame 629)
      - Amar, Salomon - Application 890044 (Reel 48, Frame 668)
      - Sevarino, Kevin A. - Application 890045 (Reel 48, Frame 697)
      - Nickerson, Katherine G. - Application 890046 (Reel 48, Frame 734)
      - Thom, David H. - Application 890047 (Reel 48, Frame 766)
      - Boulton, Amy H. - Application 890048 (Reel 48, Frame 798)
      - Wilhelmsen, Kirk C. - Application 890049 (Reel 48, Frame 832)
      - Meador-Woodruff, James H. - Application 890050 (Reel 48, Frame 863)
      - Tunkel, Allan R. - Application 890051 (Reel 48, Frame 904)
      - Colomer, Ramon - Application 890052 (Reel 48, Frame 939)
      - Siu, Gerald - Application 890053 (Reel 48, Frame 977)
      - Cyert, Martha S. - Application 890054 (Reel 48, Frame 1008)
      - Krummen, Lynne A. - Application 890055 (Reel 48, Frame 1038)
      - Paris, Joseph M. - Application 890056 (Reel 48, Frame 1076)
      - Brown, Abraham M. - Application 890057 (Reel 48, Frame 1115)
      - Pines, Jonathon W. - Application 890059 (Reel 48, Frame 1144)
      - Rogers, Scott W. - Application 890060 (Reel 48, Frame 1176)
      - Gibbs, Robert B. - Application 890061 (Reel 49, Frame 1)
      - Bangs, James D. - Application 890062 (Reel 49, Frame 33)
      - Keller, Asaf - Application 890063 (Reel 49, Frame 62)
      - Hayes, Diane - Application 890064 (Reel 49, Frame 94)
      - Quackenbush, Laurie J. - Application 890065 (Reel 49, Frame 124)
      - Schoepfer, Ralf - Application 890066 (Reel 49, Frame 163)
      - Rock, Barbara M. - Application 890067 (Reel 49, Frame 193)
      - Dorit, Robert L. - Application 890068 (Reel 49, Frame 230)
      - Perkins, Robert L. - Application 890068 (Reel 49, Frame 262)
      - Tapscott, Stephen J. - Application 890070 (Reel 49, Frame 291)
      - Perris, Roberto - Application 890071 (Reel 49, Frame 318)
      - Gelman, Irwin H. - Application 890072 (Reel 49, Frame 353)
      - Kim, Jae S. - Application 890073 (Reel 49, Frame 383)
      - Copeland, Constance S. - Application 890074 (Reel 49, Frame 414)
      - Fulwiler, Carl - Application 890075 (Reel 49, Frame 448)
      - Huang, Shau-Ku - Application 890076 (Reel 49, Frame 480)
      - Krueger, James G. - Application 890078 (Reel 49, Frame 510)
      - Barres, Barbara A. - Application 890079 (Reel 49, Frame 547)
      - Kurtzman, Gary J. - Application 890080 (Reel 49, Frame 592)
      - Liu, Chau-Ching - Application 890081 (Reel 49, Frame 626)
      - Citovsky, Vitaly - Application 890083 (Reel 49, Frame 659)
      - Kern, Marialice - Application 890084 (Reel 49, Frame 693)
      - Drain, Charles M. - Application 890085 (Reel 49, Frame 724)
      - Volpp, Bryan D. - Application 890087 (Reel 49, Frame 752)
      - Leonard, Claire M. - Application 890088 (Reel 49, Frame 782)
      - Ikuta, Koichi - Application 890090 (Reel 49, Frame 818)
      - Tarantal, Alice F. - Application 890091 (Reel 49, Frame 849)
      - Case, John P. - Application 890093 (Reel 49, Frame 881)
      - Dai, Wei - Application 890094 (Reel 49, Frame 918)
      - Zelenetz, Andrew D. - Application 890095 (Reel 49, Frame 947)
      - Hager, Karl M. - Application 890096 (Reel 49, Frame 981)
      - Koonce, Michael P. - Application 890097 (Reel 49, Frame 1013)
      - Colley, Karen J. - Application 890098 (Reel 49, Frame 1043)
      - Glick, Adam B. - Application 890099 (Reel 49, Frame 1076)
      - Andrew, Deborah J. - Application 890100 (Reel 49, Frame 1105)
      - Laffan, John J., III - Application 890102 (Reel 49, Frame 1141)
      - Meininger, Cynthia J. - Application 890103 (Reel 49, Frame 1173)
      - Brill, Steven J. - Application 890104 (Reel 50, Frame 1)
      - Roberts, Veronica J. - Application 890105 (Reel 50, Frame 27)
      - Hampton, Robert E. - Application 890106 (Reel 50, Frame 61)
      - Marriott, Susan - Application 890107 (Reel 50, Frame 94)
      - Zhu, Duzhang - Application 890108 (Reel 50, Frame 128)
      - Pannabecker, Thomas L. - Application 890109 (Reel 50, Frame 157)
      - Bristow, Cindy L. - Application 890110 (Reel 50, Frame 183)
      - McGookey, Dianna J. - Application 890111 (Reel 50, Frame 213)
      - Balkan, Wayne - Application 890112 (Reel 50, Frame 244)
      - Zeng, Gengsheng L. - Application 890113 (Reel 50, Frame 274)
      - Garber, Sarah S. - Application 890114 (Reel 50, Frame 303)
      - Ennis, Matthew - Application 890115 (Reel 50, Frame 336)
      - Kron, Michael A. - Application 890116 (Reel 50, Frame 364)
      - Hart, Susan G. E. - Application 890117 (Reel 50, Frame 401)
      - Thaler, David S. - Application 890118 (Reel 50, Frame 436)
      - Danto, Spencer I. - Application 890119 (Reel 50, Frame 468)
      - Dumenco, Luba L. - Application 890120 (Reel 50, Frame 500)
      - Pauli, Daniel R. - Application 890121 (Reel 50, Frame 538)
      - Jeyasingham, Marina D. - Application 890122 (Reel 50, Frame 569)
      - Telfer, Evelyn E. - Application 890123 (Reel 50, Frame 604)
      - Fenjves, Elizabeth - Application 890124 (Reel 50, Frame 634)
      - Kuo, Scot C. - Application 890125 (Reel 50, Frame 665)
      - Greenamyre, John T. - Application 890126 (Reel 50, Frame 695)
      - Cruikshank, William W. - Application 890127 (Reel 50, Frame 739)
      - Sullender, Wayne M. - Application 890128 (Reel 50, Frame 771)
      - Carlson, Sonia L. - Application 890129 (Reel 50, Frame 805)
      - Schapira, Ralph M. - Application 890130 (Reel 50, Frame 840)
      - Jakubowski, Moshe - Application 890131 (Reel 50, Frame 869)
      - Kiel, Jeffrey W. - Application 890132 (Reel 50, Frame 903)
      - Emerson, Ronald B. - Application 890133 (Reel 50, Frame 935)
      - Horowitz, Arie - Application 890134 (Reel 50, Frame 964)
      - Perkins, Archibald S. - Application 890135 (Reel 50, Frame 999)
      - Harding, Clifford V., III - Application 890136 (Reel 50, Frame 1031)
      - Karpen, Gary H. - Application 890137 (Reel 50, Frame 1060)
      - Heck, Margarete M. S. - Application 890138 (Reel 50, Frame 1091)
      - Tower, John G. - Application 890139 (Reel 50, Frame 1121)
      - Ingalls, Hilary M. - Application 890140 (Reel 50, Frame 1149)
      - Carpenter, Christopher L. - Application 890141 (Reel 50, Frame 1175)
      - Koury, Stephen T. - Application 890142 (Reel 50, Frame 1202)
      - Ross, Brian D. - Application 890143 (Reel 51, Frame 1)
      - Badger, John - Application 890144 (Reel 51, Frame 37)
      - Israel, Jonathan L. - Application 890145 (Reel 51, Frame 66)
      - Dooley, Michael P. - Application 890146 (Reel 51, Frame 96)
      - Davis, Janet E. - Application 890147 (Reel 51, Frame 134)
      - Roubenoff, Ronenn - Application 890148 (Reel 51, Frame 168)
      - Mulligan, Kathleen A. - Application 890149 (Reel 51, Frame 204)
      - George, Alfred L., Jr. - Application 890150 (Reel 51, Frame 240)
      - Bender, Alex S. - Application 890151 (Reel 51, Frame 275)
      - Reed, Robert A. - Application 890152 (Reel 51, Frame 306)
      - Silverman, Gary A. - Application 890153 (Reel 51, Frame 336)
      - Goldenring, James R. - Application 890154 (Reel 51, Frame 373)
      - Badamchian, Mahnaz - Application 890155 (Reel 51, Frame 423)
      - Scarsdale, Joe N., Jr. - Application 890156 (Reel 51, Frame 468)
      - Judge, Kevin W. - Application 890157 (Reel 51, Frame 498)
      - Tseng-Crank, Julie C. L. - Application 890159 (Reel 51, Frame 528)
      - Osei, Peter - Application 890160 (Reel 51, Frame 561)
      - Carver, Wayne E. - Application 890161 (Reel 51, Frame 587)
      - Goodman, Steven L. - Application 890162 (Reel 51, Frame 620)
      - Downs, Diana M. - Application 890163 (Reel 51, Frame 651)
      - Joseph, Jon - Application 890164 (Reel 51, Frame 684)
      - Baranski, Bruce G. - Application 890165 (Reel 51, Frame 711)
      - Barnard, Joseph W. - Application 890166 (Reel 51, Frame 743)
      - Pierce, Mark A. - Application 890167 (Reel 51, Frame 773)
      - Gauthier, V. Joyce - Application 890168 (Reel 51, Frame 802)
      - Dominey, Andrea M. - Application 890169 (Reel 51, Frame 838)
      - Buck, Charles R. - Application 890170 (Reel 51, Frame 864)
      - Geraghty, Daniel E. - Application 890171 (Reel 51, Frame 898)
      - Pierce, Mary E. - Application 890172 (Reel 51, Frame 924)
      - Van Dongen, Antonius M. - Application 890173 (Reel 51, Frame 959)
      - Anderson, Pamela W. - Application 890174 (Reel 51, Frame 994)
      - McCurdy, Deborah K. - Application 890175 (Reel 51, Frame 1028)
      - Jayasena, Sumedha - Application 890176 (Reel 51, Frame 1064)
      - Burne, Robert A. - Application 890177 (Reel 51, Frame 1091)
      - Koretzky, Gary A. - Application 890178 (Reel 51, Frame 1129)
      - Hyman, Anthony - Application 890180 (Reel 51, Frame 1164)
      - Lidofsky, Steven - Application 890181 (Reel 51, Frame 1192)
      - Kaufman, Daniel L. - Application 890184 (Reel 52, Frame 1)
      - Ballabio, Andrea - Application 890185 (Reel 52, Frame 38)
      - Amatruda, Thomas T., III - Application 890186 (Reel 52, Frame 79)
      - Swerdlow, Neal R. - Application 900001 (Reel 52, Frame 113)
      - Travali, Salvatore - Application 900002 (Reel 52, Frame 163)
      - Powell, Leland D. - Application 900003 (Reel 52, Frame 177)
      - Walter, Mark R. - Application 900004 (Reel 52, Frame 209)
      - Guatelli, John C. - Application 900005 (Reel 52, Frame 236)
      - Wade, Rebecca C. - Application 900006 (Reel 52, Frame 271)
      - Selmin, Ornella - Application 900007 (Reel 52, Frame 299)
      - Hollman, Michael - Application 900008 (Reel 52, Frame 334)
      - Bosner, Matthew S. - Application 900009 (Reel 52, Frame 367)
      - Neidle, Ellen L. - Application 900010 (Reel 52, Frame 401)
      - Glazer, Peter M. - Application 900011 (Reel 52, Frame 432)
      - Wahls, Wayne P. - Application 900012 (Reel 52, Frame 461)
      - Yeh, Hung-Yueh - Application 900013 (Reel 52, Frame 491)
      - Keck, James G. - Application 900014 (Reel 52, Frame 521)
      - Roth, David B. - Application 900015 (Reel 52, Frame 554)
      - Patel, Mona - Application 900016 (Reel 52, Frame 585)
      - Countryman, Jill K. - Application 900017 (Reel 52, Frame 612)
      - Pugh, Benjamin F. - Application 900019 (Reel 52, Frame 647)
      - Weaver, Arthur J. - Application 900020 (Reel 52, Frame 675)
      - Stayton, Patrick S. - Application 900021 (Reel 52, Frame 704)
      - Zeitler, Philip S. - Application 900022 (Reel 52, Frame 736)
      - Zhu, Duzhang - Application 900023 (Reel 52, Frame 770)
      - Chao, Anna T. - Application 900024 (Reel 52, Frame 803)
      - Shenoy, Suresh - Application 900025 (Reel 52, Frame 835)
      - Han, Myun Ki - Application 900026 (Reel 52, Frame 861)
      - El-Ashry, Dorraya - Application 900027 (Reel 52, Frame 896)
      - Lupu, Ruth - Application 900028 (Reel 52, Frame 925)
      - Garrett, Lenora R. - Application 900029 (Reel 52, Frame 966)
      - Merchant, Kalpana M. - Application 900030 (Reel 52, Frame 995)
      - Backer, Jonathan M. - Application 900031 (Reel 52, Frame 1033)
      - McCauley, Laurie K. - Application 900032 (Reel 52, Frame 1069)
      - Byrd, Sherrell K. - Application 900034 (Reel 52, Frame 1106)
      - Yamanishi, Douglas T. - Application 900035 (Reel 52, Frame 1144)
      - Bowerman, Bruce A. - Application 900036 (Reel 52, Frame 1176)
      - Morton, Mary E. - Application 900037 (Reel 53, Frame 1)
      - Kramer, Helmut - Application 900038 (Reel 53, Frame 29)
      - Carlson, Cathy S. - Application 900039 (Reel 53, Frame 57)
      - Lee, Se-Jim - Application 900040 (Reel 53, Frame 92)
      - Rogers, Patricia V. - Application 900041 (Reel 53, Frame 121)
      - Hockett, Richard D., Jr. - Application 900042 (Reel 53, Frame 151)
      - Golde, William T. - Application 900043 (Reel 53, Frame 177)
      - Barford, David - Application 900045 (Reel 53, Frame 213)
      - Liang, Zhi-Pei - Application 900046 (Reel 53, Frame 243)
      - Bancroft, John D. - Application 900047 (Reel 53, Frame 273)
      - Wierner, Michael C. - Application 900049 (Reel 53, Frame 307)
      - Arden, Warwick A. - Application 900050 (Reel 53, Frame 343)
      - Cezeaux, Judy L. - Application 900051 (Reel 53, Frame 375)
      - Scarsdale, Joe N., Jr. - Application 900052 (Reel 53, Frame 402)
      - Chapman, Michael S. - Application 900053 (Reel 53, Frame 433)
      - Glenny, Robb W. - Application 900054 (Reel 53, Frame 471)
      - Evans, James P. - Application 900055 (Reel 53, Frame 513)
      - Yakel, Jerrel L. - Application 900056 (Reel 53, Frame 548)
      - Liu, Yeuchueng - Application 900057 (Reel 53, Frame 579)
      - van der Bliek, Alexander M. - Application 900058 (Reel 53, Frame 605)
      - Conway, Gregory C. - Application 900059 (Reel 53, Frame 636)
      - Weigel, Detlef - Application 900062 (Reel 53, Frame 666)
      - Norris, David N. - Application 900063 (Reel 53, Frame 697)
      - Ponticelli, Alfred S. - Application 900064 (Reel 53, Frame 729)
      - Kellis, James T., Jr. - Application 900065 (Reel 53, Frame 760)
      - Magness, Linda - Application 900067 (Reel 53, Frame 791)
      - Von Bartheld, Christopher S. - Application 900068 (Reel 53, Frame 821)
      - Jordan, Cynthia L. - Application 900071 (Reel 53, Frame 855)
      - Voss, Anne K. - Application 900072 (Reel 53, Frame 887)
      - Morimoto, Bruce H. - Application 900073 (Reel 53, Frame 914)
      - Pillai, Radhakrishna - Application 900074 (Reel 53, Frame 943)
      - Novicki, Andrea - Application 900075 (Reel 53, Frame 972)
      - Grompe, Markus - Application 900076 (Reel 53, Frame 1000)
      - Ono, Santa J. - Application 900077 (Reel 53, Frame 1040)
      - Gesek, Frank A. - Application 900078 (Reel 53, Frame 1073)
      - Sherley, James L. - Application 900080 (Reel 53, Frame 1110)
      - Peifer, Mark A. - Application 900081 (Reel 53, Frame 1137)
      - Smith, Jonathan D. - Application 900082 (Reel 53, Frame 1167)
      - Frendl, Gyorgy - Application 900083 (Reel 53, Frame 1194)
      - Schultze, Albert E. - Application 900084 (Reel 54, Frame 1)
      - McClellan-Green, Patrick D. - Application 900085 (Reel 54, Frame 38)
      - Kayne, Laurie H. - Application 900086 (Reel 54, Frame 73)
      - Nambu, John R. - Application 900087 (Reel 54, Frame 105)
      - Clemens, Daniel L. - Application 900088 (Reel 54, Frame 136)
      - Rodriguez, Beatriz L. - Application 900089 (Reel 54, Frame 169)
      - Barnard, Michele L. - Application 900090 (Reel 54, Frame 203)
      - Nicchitta, Christopher V. - Application 900092 (Reel 54, Frame 232)
      - Fletcher, Colin - Application 900093 (Reel 54, Frame 260)
      - Plautz, Gregory E. - Application 900094 (Reel 54, Frame 288)
      - Pittler, Steven J. - Application 900095 (Reel 54, Frame 316)
      - Mark, Gregory P. - Application 900096 (Reel 54, Frame 353)
      - Wilk, Boguslawa - Application 900097 (Reel 54, Frame 382)
      - Thayer, Mathew James - Application 900098 (Reel 54, Frame 413)
      - Ericson, Solveig G. - Application 900099 (Reel 54, Frame 443)
      - Siwek, Donald F. - Application 900100 (Reel 54, Frame 469)
      - Lozier, Jay N. - Application 900101 (Reel 54, Frame 499)
      - Morris, Andrew J. - Application 900102 (Reel 54, Frame 533)
      - Ha, Belinda - Application 900103 (Reel 54, Frame 565)
      - Roberts, Kenneth P. - Application 900104 (Reel 54, Frame 597)
      - Pluta, Ann F. - Application 900105 (Reel 54, Frame 629)
      - Welling, Paul A. - Application 900106 (Reel 54, Frame 656)
      - Walker, Vernon E. - Application 900107 (Reel 54, Frame 687)
      - Kaplan, Andrew H. - Application 900108 (Reel 54, Frame 735)
      - Muller, Daniel - Application 900109 (Reel 54, Frame 765)
      - Dolphin, William F. - Application 900110 (Reel 54, Frame 796)
      - Ervasti, James M. - Application 900112 (Reel 54, Frame 835)
      - Oliver, Brian C. - Application 900113 (Reel 54, Frame 868)
      - Baker, David - Application 900115 (Reel 54, Frame 896)
      - Giniger, Edward - Application 900116 (Reel 54, Frame 923)
      - Honigberg, Saul M. - Application 900118 (Reel 54, Frame 954)
      - Emanuel, Peter D. - Application 900119 (Reel 54, Frame 986)
      - Pines, Jonathon N. - Application 900120 (Reel 54, Frame 1024)
      - Kaufman, Daniel L. - Application 900121 (Reel 54, Frame 1052)
      - Noble, Paul W. - Application 900122 (Reel 54, Frame 1083)
      - Edberg, Jeffrey C. - Application 900123 (Reel 54, Frame 1124)
      - LeSauter, Joseph - Application 900124 (Reel 54, Frame 1160)
      - Albertini, Mark R. - Application 900125 (Reel 55, Frame 1)
      - Holy, Jon M. - Application 900126 (Reel 55, Frame 38)
      - Blackwell, Thomas K. - Application 900127 (Reel 55, Frame 73)
      - Bordi, Fabio - Application 900128 (Reel 55, Frame 104)
      - Sherman, John C. - Application 900129 (Reel 55, Frame 134)
      - Rada, Jody A. - Application 900130 (Reel 55, Frame 162)
      - Hoops, Timothy C. - Application 900131 (Reel 55, Frame 195)
      - Lim, Dongbin - Application 900132 (Reel 55, Frame 227)
      - Reid, R. Clay - Application 900133 (Reel 55, Frame 260)
      - Levy, Joan B. - Application 900134 (Reel 55, Frame 290)
      - Hall, Alison K. - Application 900135 (Reel 55, Frame 321)
      - Portis, Lisa R. - Application 900136 (Reel 55, Frame 350)
      - Drain, Charles M. - Application 900137 (Reel 55, Frame 377)
      - Vann, James M. - Application 900138 (Reel 55, Frame 403)
      - Martin, Jennifer M. - Application 900139 (Reel 55, Frame 435)
      - Jang, Sung Key - Application 900140 (Reel 55, Frame 467)
      - Walbert, Mark W. - Application 900141 (Reel 55, Frame 501)
      - Bliska, James B. - Application 900142 (Reel 55, Frame 530)
      - Joseph, Bobby Z. - Application 900143 (Reel 55, Frame 563)
      - Mangoura, Dimitra A. - Application 900144 (Reel 55, Frame 596)
      - Lovejoy, Jennifer - Application 900145 (Reel 55, Frame 636)
      - Ngai, John H. - Application 900146 (Reel 55, Frame 668)
      - Miller, Ann-Frances - Application 900147 (Reel 55, Frame 697)
      - Akoury, Dalal A. - Application 900148 (Reel 55, Frame 726)
      - Pant, Nalin - Application 900149 (Reel 55, Frame 758)
      - Waller, Edmund K. - Application 900150 (Reel 55, Frame 788)
      - Jackson, Bruce A. - Application 900151 (Reel 55, Frame 820)
      - Gober, James W. - Application 900152 (Reel 55, Frame 850)
      - Rubenstein, John L. R. - Application 900153 (Reel 55, Frame 878)
      - O'Donnell, Amy L. - Application 900155 (Reel 55, Frame 912)
      - Pierson, Myles E., Jr. - Application 900156 (Reel 55, Frame 938)
      - LaRue, Susan M. - Application 900157 (Reel 55, Frame 973)
      - Lopez, Suzanne M. - Application 900158 (Reel 55, Frame 1006)
      - Lee, Vaughan H. - Application 900159 (Reel 55, Frame 1044)
      - Radic, Marko Z. - Application 900160 (Reel 55, Frame 1075)
      - Ramasamy, Ravichandran - Application 900161 (Reel 55, Frame 1105)
      - Salazar-Grueso, Edgar F. - Application 900162 (Reel 55, Frame 1139)
      - Rens-Domiano, Stephanie - Application 900163 (Reel 55, Frame 1180)
      - McKenzie, Steve E. - Application 900165 (Reel 56, Frame 1)
      - Barr, Frederic G. - Application 900166 (Reel 56, Frame 32)
      - Benko, Donna M. - Application 900167 (Reel 56, Frame 70)